<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cosplay on Robin Wang</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/cosplay/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cosplay on Robin Wang</description>
    <image>
      <title>Robin Wang</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.128.1</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 03:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/cosplay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Subnautica Survival Knife</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/subnautica-knife/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 03:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/subnautica-knife/</guid>
      <description>This is 1:1 replica of the iconic survival knife from the game subnautica.
Table of Contents Overview Inspiration In Game Reference CAD Prototyping Blade Fabrication Laser Cutting Electro Etching Edge Grinding Vacuum Furanace Heat Treating DIY Hardening Professional Hardening Chemical Laser Etching Sharpening Handle Fabrication 3D Printing Resin Casting Final Assembly Packaging Cost/Stats Material Costs Tools Costs Service Fees Revenue Profit(?) Conclusion Overview This was my first project into blade smithing and low volume mass production, as well as my first attempt at selling a product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subnautica Spy Pengling</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/spy-pengling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 03:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/spy-pengling/</guid>
      <description>This is 1:1 functional replica of the spy pengling robot from the game Subnautica - Below Zero.
Overview This was my first large scale CAD assembly design. I wanted to make it as accurate as possible but also functional so I could drive it around like an RC car. Looking back, it shows hows crude my manufacturing techniques were but gave invaluable insight into how to better design robots.
CAD Model Drivetrain track pods each housing two brushed motorsThe CAD model can be divided into three primary sections which are the drivetrain, body, and head.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
