<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Plane on Robin Wang</title>
    <link>https://robinwang.github.io/categories/plane/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Plane on Robin Wang</description>
    <image>
      <title>Robin Wang</title>
      <url>https://robinwang.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://robinwang.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.128.1</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 03:24:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://robinwang.github.io/categories/plane/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Long Endurance Fixed Wing Camera Platform</title>
      <link>https://robinwang.github.io/posts/mfe-believer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 03:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://robinwang.github.io/posts/mfe-believer/</guid>
      <description>A autonomous, long endurance, high altitude camera platform for gimballed fpv
Overview I planned out this aircraft to solely focus on efficiency and stable flight performance. With a 5.5Kg max takeoff weight and two 6s 10aH lipo batteries, this aircraft can stay in the air for over 3 hours. Swap one of the batteries for a downward facing DSLR camera and the aircraft becomes a capable mapping platform. Control is handled via the latest H7 processor running arduplane firmware enabling the aircraft to navigate autonomously, accept waypoint missions, and operate a three axis gimbal installed in the nose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Payload Fixed Wing Testbed</title>
      <link>https://robinwang.github.io/posts/skywalker-titan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 03:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://robinwang.github.io/posts/skywalker-titan/</guid>
      <description>A high capacity cargo platform capable of lifting test equipment into the air remain on station for extended periods of time.
Overview The purpose of this airframe is to test experimental avionics and payloads. The airframe has high internal volume to fit bulky cargo as well as hardpoints on both wings for external loads. While the original intention was for this plane to fly, I&amp;rsquo;ve deemed the risk too high and as such, this airframe is to remain on the ground for testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tricopter VTOL</title>
      <link>https://robinwang.github.io/posts/tricopter-vtol/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 03:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://robinwang.github.io/posts/tricopter-vtol/</guid>
      <description>A small tricopter vtol allowing for fun fixed wing FPV out of areas that lack runway space
Overview This project was my introduction into ardupilots and autonomous flight. Prior to this, all my models were simple RC planes which were either entirely manually controlled or had limited flight stabilization built into the receivers. It was a steep learning curve to start with a vtol but provided an excellent teaching experience.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
